{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "My computer __________ every time I open Visual Studio.",
      "answers": ["Dies", "Crashes", "Blocks", "Shuts off"],
      "correctIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Organisations are __________ turning to algorithms to automate or support decision-making.",
      "answers": ["Progressively", "Growingly", "Increasingly", "Increasing"],
      "correctIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Google has an Application programming interface (API) that __________ users to get information about maps.",
      "answers": ["Authorizes", "Allows", "Gives access to", "Facilitates"],
      "correctIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Data structure provides a way of organizing, managing, and storing data __________.",
      "answers": ["Efficiently", "Methodically", "Coherently", "Dexterously"],
      "correctIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the error I got \"Segmentation Fault (Core __________)\" in the C language?",
      "answers": ["Erroneous", "Dumped", "Thrown away", "Dump"],
      "correctIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "The time complexity is the amount of time __________ by an algorithm to run, as a function of the length of the input.",
      "answers": ["Forced", "Consumed", "Laid hold of", "Taken"],
      "correctIndex": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "A client-server system is a system in which some computers (the clients), __________ services provided by other computers, the servers.",
      "answers": ["Demand", "Ask for", "Request", "Call"],
      "correctIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Cyber security is the practice of defending computers, servers, mobile devices, electronic systems, networks, and data from __________ attacks.",
      "answers": ["Malicious", "Viral", "Risky", "Bad"],
      "correctIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "If you get back late, I __________  angry.",
      "answers": ["will have been", "will be", "would be", "was"],
      "correctIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "I have __________ three essays this week.",
      "answers": ["had written", "wrote", "written", "will write"],
      "correctIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "If I _________  you, I would get a new job.",
      "answers": ["were", "was", "will be", "have been"],
      "correctIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "We __________ too much chocolate.",
      "answers": ["ate", "have eaten", "will eat", "had eaten"],
      "correctIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "I __________  my football team would win.",
      "answers": ["will think", "have thought", "had thought", "thought"],
      "correctIndex": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "We __________  to the cinema tonight.",
      "answers": ["hadn’t gone", "won’t go", "haven’t gone", "aren't going"],
      "correctIndex": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "If we had arrived earlier, we __________ John.",
      "answers": ["had seen", "saw", "would have seen", "have seen"],
      "correctIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "I ___________ there long when she quit.",
      "answers": [
        "wasn’t working",
        "hadn't been working",
        "didn’t work",
        "haven’t work"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "If he ______________ a musician, he would have recorded a CD.",
      "answers": ["have become", "had become", "will become", "became"],
      "correctIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "He was working in the garden when he ___________ the money.",
      "answers": ["had found", "have found", "found", "will find"],
      "correctIndex": 2
    }
  ]
}
